[
  {
    "question": "What is a sailor's striped clothing called?",
    "answer": "vest",
    "allAnswers": [
      "vest",
      "sweatshirt",
      "T-shirt",
      "peakless cap"
    ],
    "amount": "500",
    "id": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "How do tulips reproduce?",
    "answer": "bulbs",
    "allAnswers": [
      "bulbs",
      "carrots",
      "beets",
      "heads of cabbage"
    ],
    "amount": "1,000",
    "id": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the largest desert located?",
    "answer": "in Antarctica",
    "allAnswers": [
      "in Antarctica",
      "in Africa",
      "in America",
      "in Ukraine"
    ],
    "amount": "2,000",
    "id": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "The exhibition of which artist was visited by the heroine of the song \"Exhibit\" of the group \"Leningrad\"?",
    "answer": "Van Gogh",
    "allAnswers": [
      "Van Gogh",
      "Gauguin",
      "Matisse",
      "Renoir"
    ],
    "amount": "4,000",
    "id": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "In whom, according to the myth, the goddess Hera turned the hundred-eyed giant Argus?",
    "answer": "in a peacock",
    "allAnswers": [
      "in a peacock",
      "in a leopard",
      "in a centaur",
      "in whale"
    ],
    "amount": "8,000",
    "id": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "The object for which sports game in India was called the \"ball-flower\"?",
    "answer": "badminton",
    "allAnswers": [
      "badminton",
      "golf",
      "field hockey",
      "cricket"
    ],
    "amount": "16,000",
    "id": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these devices appeared later than the others?",
    "answer": "multicooker",
    "allAnswers": [
      "multicooker",
      "toaster",
      "meat grinder",
      "microwave oven"
    ],
    "amount": "32,000",
    "id": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of performance does a medley relay usually start with?",
    "answer": "on the back",
    "allAnswers": [
      "on the back",
      "freestyle",
      "breaststroke",
      "butterfly"
    ],
    "amount": "64,000",
    "id": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What did actress Jane Birkin like to wear in her purse instead of her purse?",
    "answer": "in the basket",
    "allAnswers": [
      "in the basket",
      "in a string bag",
      "in a plastic bag",
      "in a duffel bag"
    ],
    "amount": "125,000",
    "id": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What did the new owners of Banksy's Morons (White) do with it after it was bought at auction?",
    "answer": "burned",
    "allAnswers": [
      "burned",
      "painted over",
      "signed",
      "buried in the ground"
    ],
    "amount": "250,000",
    "id": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What are tips that are especially valued by tea pickers?",
    "answer": "kidneys",
    "allAnswers": [
      "kidneys",
      "leaves",
      "flowers",
      "stem parts"
    ],
    "amount": "500,000",
    "id": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country was the Sun Drop gemstone found?",
    "answer": "South Africa",
    "allAnswers": [
      "South Africa",
      "Brazil",
      "China",
      "Australia"
    ],
    "amount": "1,000,000",
    "id": 12
  }
]